Resume **Kevin Irwan**







Kevin Thomas Irwan

Studied communication and journalism, and have been working in the industry my whole proffesional life. I've grown from the typical journalist to someone who understand the depths of this field.

I've tasted both established corporate and startup companies, and has gain valuable knowledge from both experiences.

Personally, I'm a movie junkie, huge fan of sports, and have a secret passion in cooking.

Work Experience

Content Leader

Qraved - PT. Eatiki

September 2015 - Present

Starting as a Sr. Content editor, currently I lead the team that consist of 8 members.

- -Creates a strategic plan for developing the content side the company.
- -Making content plan for editorial team.
- -Producing content to be posted online.
- -Responsible with bridging other departments with content division.

Managing Editor

TalkMen - PT. Eatiki

January 2013 – April 2015

Talkmen is a men's lifestyle online media that started from December 2012. Sadly, due to lack of funding, the company is dissolved.

- -Creates a strategic plan for developing, training, and managing the editorial team.
- -Responsible for editing and QC of all the articles posted on the site.
- -Conducting presentation and meetings with potential clients regarding advertorials.

Journalist/Contributor

Hai - PT.Kompas Gramedia

November 2011 - December 2012

Most of the work that I've done in here is for the sport and music section.

-Researches, writes, and reports on information for the magazine.

linkedin.com/in/kevinirwan

Education **Contact info**

Bachelor of Communication - Broadcast Journalism University of Pelita Harapan Class of 2006

Things you should know.

Why are you seeing this CV?

Obviously I still have a job, and I won't be writing this CV is everything is perfect. There's different factors I want for my professional career, and I'm not the type of person who's afraid of a new challenge. That is why you are looking at my CV right now.

Why should you hire me?

I'm may not have an education from abroad, masters degree, or those kind of education, but I have the passion and drive to always go forward. I'm quiet confident that my experiences can cover my limitations. I can work well within a team, and also capable in stepping up to be the leader.

Phone: 085794001233 Mail: irwan.kevin@gmail.com